{
	"rounds": [
		{
			"round": 1,
			"roundName": "Round 1",
			"categories": [
				{
					"category": 1,
					"categoryName": "Characters",
					"questions": [
						{
							"question": "Sandor Clegane",
							"answer": "The Hound",
							"value": 100
						},
						{
							"question": "He knighted Brine",
							"answer": "Sir Jaime Lannister",
							"value": 200
						},
						{
							"question": "Jon Snow’s Wilding girlfriend",
							"answer": "Ygritte",
							"value": 300
						},
						{
							"question": "The Red Viper of Dorne",
							"answer": "Oberyn Martell",
							"value": 400
						},
						{
							"question": "A leiutentant in the Second Sons and Dany’s lover",
							"answer": "Daario Naharis",
							"value": 500
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"category": 2,
					"categoryName": "Who said that? (RHoATL voice)",
					"questions": [
						{
							"question": "What do dragons eat, anyway?",
							"answer": "Sansa Stark",
							"value": 100
						},
						{
							"question": "You want a whore? Buy her. You want a queen? Earn her.",
							"answer": "Cersei Lannister",
							"value": 200
						},
						{
							"question": "You gave up your crown to save your people. Would she do the same?",
							"answer": "Sawmell Tarly",
							"value": 300
						},
						{
							"question": "I always knew you were just another rich girl.",
							"answer": "Gendry",
							"value": 400
						},
						{
							"question": "Distrusting me was the wisest thing you’ve done since climbing down from your horse",
							"answer": "Petyr Baelish or Little Finger",
							"value": 500
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"category": 3,
					"categoryName": "Places",
					"questions": [
						{
							"question": "City where the Iron Throne sits",
							"answer": "King’s Landing",
							"value": 100
						},
						{
							"question": "Cersei claimed this place had never fallen",
							"answer": "The Red Keep",
							"value": 200
						},
						{
							"question": "Ruled by House Martell",
							"answer": "Dorne",
							"value": 300
						},
						{
							"question": "Home of Olenna Tyrell",
							"answer": "Highgarden",
							"value": 400
						},
						{
							"question": "Ancient castel with the Moon Door and seat of House Arryn",
							"answer": "The Eyrie",
							"value": 500
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"category": 4,
					"categoryName": "Who killed me?",
					"questions": [
						{
							"question": "Euron Greyjoy",
							"answer": "Jaime Lannister",
							"value": 100
						},
						{
							"question": "Lord Varys",
							"answer": "Drogon",
							"value": 200
						},
						{
							"question": "Shae",
							"answer": "Tyrion Lannister",
							"value": 300
						},
						{
							"question": "Lyanna Mormont",
							"answer": "Undead giant",
							"value": 400
						},
						{
							"question": "Tommen Baratheon",
							"answer": "Himself/Suicide",
							"value": 500
						}
					]  
				}
			]
		}
	]
}